https://www.talktomemen.com/privacy_policy.php

1-800-MEN-1111
Main Menu:
Outside the USA? Call +1-214-828-CHAT
Login to see your account & pin number.
Search
Menu
Are you sure you want to cancel this connection and close this window?
Yes
No
Loading, please wait ...
×
with
You are about to send a private message to . You can send a text only introductory message for free. Additional text-only messages are , and messages with attachments start at .
Continue
Don't show this info screen again
×
with
You are about to have a one-on-one private phone call with
for . Press the continue button below when you are ready to have the system connect you. If you prefer, you can also dial into the system directly and pay using your credit card without creating an account. If you are not 100% satisfied with your call experience please let us know.
Continue
Dial In
Don't show this info screen again
×
with
If you prefer to dial in call:
1-800-MEN-1111
When prompted for a profile number enter:
Go Back
×
with
You are about to have a private one-on-one text messaging session with . Prices start from only . A smart phone with texting is required to use this service. Press the continue button below when you are ready.
Continue
Don't show this info screen again
×
with
You are about to start a one-on-one chat session with
for . When you are ready to get started click the continue button below.
Continue
Don't show this info screen again
×
with
You are about to send a voicemail to
for . When you are ready to get started click the continue button below.
Continue
Don't show this info screen again
×
with
Please login to continue.
An account is required to continue beyond this point. Please create a free account or login now to continue.
Join Free
Login Now
×
with
Please verify your phone number.
Thanks for joining, we also require all new accounts to add and verify a phone number before we can connect you. Please take a moment to handle this now, you will only need to do this once.
Add a Phone Number
×
with
Your wallet is empty.
The last thing you need to do is setup your wallet on our site. Your wallet funds can be used for any service, with any talker on our site. If this is your first time you can claim $20 free with no purchase necessary just by adding a valid credit card. To connect with
you will need to add money to your account.To connect with
you will need to add money to your account, or add a credit card to pay for the call as you go.
Add Money to My Wallet
Continue with my Current Balance
Add a Credit Card
×
with
Your wallet balance is low.
Your wallet balance only has z. We recommend adding more funds to your wallet before you continue. If your balance runs out you will be disconnected.
Add Money Now
Continue with my Current Balance
Add a Credit Card
×
with
Confirm your phone call settings:
Payment Plan:
My Phone Number:
Call me at
Payment Options:
Use funds in my wallet.Use my wallet, then my credit card.Use my credit card.Credit Card:VISA - 4300 **** **** 1234
Record this Phone Call for meConnect Me NowTell me about Calls
×
with
Confirm your text message settings:
Payment Plan:
Pay $0.50 Per Message You Send
My Phone Number:
Text me at 215-460-4099
Start Texting
* International users may get billed for additional charges per text message by their cell phone provider and those charges will appear on your phone statement.
Tell me about Texting
×
with
Select a Web Chat Payment Plan:
Web Chat with me for $1.50/min
Up to 5 minutes for $8.00
Up to 10 minutes for $15.00
Up to 15 minutes for $20.00
Up to 20 minutes for $30.00
* Please don't disclose any personal information for your own safety purposes. We will never ask you for your password or credit card information!
Tell me about Web Chat
×
Manage
Add New
Rocketgate
×
Starting your
...
×
An error occured:
Continue
Last Modified: 5/23/18
This Privacy Policy forms part of the User Agreement and is incorporated by reference therein. Capitalized terms not defined herein will have the meanings set forth in the User Agreement and related policies. This Privacy Policy covers information you may provide to TalkToMeMen.com through the TalkToMeMen.com website:
what personally identifiable information of yours is collected;
what organization is collecting the information;
how the information is used;
with whom the information may be shared;
what choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information;
what kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the company’s control; and
how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Your Privacy is very important to us at TalkToMeMen.com. At TalkToMeMen.com, we are committed to maintaining the trust and confidence of the visitors to our website. In particular, we want you to know that TalkToMeMen.com is not in the business of selling, renting, or trading email lists with other companies and businesses for marketing purposes.
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact TalkToMeMen.com by sending an email to support@talktome.com.
This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we’ve prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about TalkToMeMen.com’s practices so that you can make an informed decision.
1. A Special Note About Children
2. Security
3. Information TalkToMeMen.com Collects
4. Our Disclosure of Your Information
5. User Account Cancellation Procedures
6. Notification of Changes to our Privacy Policy
A Special Note About Children.
Entry to this Site requires age verification. TalkToMeMen.com requires all Users and users to be at least eighteen (18) years old to use any area of the TalkToMeMen.com Site and requires that all Users and Users agree to the terms of the Age Verification Agreement. Children are not eligible to use TalkToMeMen.com and we ask that minors (under the age of eighteen (18)) not to submit any personal information to us.
Security.
2.1. TalkToMeMen.com has certain security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL), which digitally encrypts your information as it is transferred from your computer to TalkToMeMen.com. We take the following measures to protect user information once it is received by the Site:
employees have limited and controlled access to User information;
measures have been taken so that servers and the data stored thereon are in a secure physical location;
security software is used where TalkToMeMen.com determines it to be both appropriate and cost effective;
employees are informed of all security protocol on a regular basis; and
web security procedures are quality-assured weekly.
2.2. Although we strive to keep your personal information secure, no security measures are absolute and fool-proof and there is always a possibility that a security breach could occur, resulting in the release of a User’s data or information.
Information TalkToMeMen.com Collects.
3.1. Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth and efficient experience while you’re using TalkToMeMen.com’s website services, and to keep you informed of opportunities available on those services. This allows us to provide services and features that are designed to meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier and quicker. To this end, we may share information you provide with TalkToMeMen.com-related entities worldwide, eg. its parents, affiliates, partners, joint venturers, correspondents, associates and subsidiaries and their successors and assigns (collectively herein “TalkToMeMen.com Entities”).
3.2. When you join TalkToMeMen.com using our online registration form, or by registering over the phone, we may collect your email address, User name, real name, password, phone number, and other personal information listed in the registration form. Your User name is used throughout TalkToMeMen.com to identify you to other Users. Therefore, you should be aware that if you use your real name as your User name, this information will be visible to others who visit the Site. You can also join TalkToMeMen.com via co-branded pages or co-branded phone numbers using the co-branded registration forms available on such pages or phone numbers. TalkToMeMen.com will only use the information you provide to TalkToMeMen.com by joining TalkToMeMen.com through co-branded online registration forms, phone registration, and through TalkToMeMen.com’s online registration form in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you register as a User through any co-branded pages or phone numbers, TalkToMeMen.com may share your information with the partnering entity listed on the co-branded page. Prior to completing the registration on any co-branded page or phone number, TalkToMeMen.com will notify you if your information will be shared with the partnering entity listed on the co-branded page or phone number. By completing the registration on a co-branded page or phone number, you consent to TalkToMeMen.com’s disclosure of your information in accordance with the notices displayed during the co-branded registration process. In such event, the use of your information by the partnering entity will be subject to the terms and conditions of such partnering entity’s privacy policy, which may be less restrictive than this Privacy Policy.
3.3. Because we connect Users by telephone, we require you to enter a valid telephone number to connect with other Users through TalkToMeMen.com. At no time will we share your telephone number with any other Users with whom you communicate. Because TalkToMeMen.com initiates all calls, other Users cannot see your telephone number not even with Caller ID.
3.4. We may use your email, mailing address, and phone number to contact you regarding account activities, new product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of TalkToMeMen.com and its affiliates. If you do not wish to receive such communications from TalkToMeMen.com you have the ability to stop receiving these mail communications by providing your User name and email address in a Customer Support Form or by unchecking the box on the My Preferences page, which asks if you wish to receive such mailings. You will, however, always receive administrative emails from TalkToMeMen.com that are related to the usage and functionality of TalkToMeMen.com. You may not opt-out of these administrative emails unless you cancel your Usership.
3.4.1. SMS Text Messaging Terms & Conditions
Please read these SMS/Text Messaging Terms & Conditions carefully. By completing the verifying your number on the phone manager, you expressly consent to receive non-marketing and marketing text messages from TalkToMeMen.com, including text messages made with an Auto dialer, at the mobile phone number(s) you provide. You may opt-out of these communications at any time by replying STOP to any text message from SITE or by otherwise contacting the SITE as indicated below. You can receive help at any time by replying HELP to any text message from the SITE or by otherwise contacting SITE as indicated below. Consent to receive non-marketing or marketing text messages is not required to purchase any products or services from the SITE. Messaging and data rates may apply. By completing the phone manager verification, you also accept and agree to be bound by these SMS Text Messaging Terms & Conditions and any other applicable terms and agreements related to your use of SITE services.
3.5. If you have a Talker listing and/or are earning money on TalkToMeMen.com, we collect additional information from you in order to
process and remit to you your Talker fees and/or verify your personal and/or listing information. We collect your mailing address to remit payments, and we collect your Social Security number and/or Federal Tax ID number to prepare Form 1099-MISC if necessary and to help us verify your identity. Users who are not United States taxpayers will not be asked for their Social Security numbers or Federal Tax ID numbers, though they may need to report income to their local tax authority and may be required to provide equivalent evidence of their identity.
3.6. TalkToMeMen.com may collect credit card information, add money to your User account, or use your credit card to take advantage of special promotions. TalkToMeMen.com uses RocketGate to process credit cards for billing purposes. This third party may store or retain a User’s personally identifiable information, Your credit card is not stored by TalkToMeMen.com on our site or servers. In certain cases, we will also use your partial credit card information to help us verify your identity. We do not charge or bill the credit card when we collect partial credit card information for identity verification purposes.
Please refer to RocketGate's Privacy Policy for any questions regarding your stored payment information with them.
3.7. You can review, update and change some of your personally identifiable information including your email address, date of birth, and PIN number on the My Account page. You can review, update, or change your address and credit card information by going to the Add Money page on the Site, clicking on the “New Card,” and then adding your name, address, and new or corrected card number. You may correct, update, or hide any of your TalkToMeMen.com profiles by clicking on the profile name on the Account Dashboard page. You may also update, correct, or delete information by filling out an updated Customer Support Form or you may write to TalkToMeMen.com at Customer Support, TalkToMeMen.com,
110 South 7th Street, Philadelphia, PA
19106.
3.8. You may also provide TalkToMeMen.com with additional profile information (such as experience, affiliations, on-call schedule, etc.) that is displayed publicly on the Site, on your home page, or in your listings. Other than the profile information submitted by our Users, and except as noted herein, TalkToMeMen.com does not disclose any personally identifying information to other Users without your permission. If you choose to use TalkToMeMen.com forums, know that any personally identifiable information that you post can be read, collected, or used by others, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information that you provide.
3.9. We use information we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve disputes, identify potential liabilities, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look at your User account information and transaction history to identify problems or resolve disputes. To have your account, personal information and transaction history erased from our records, please submit your request in writing:
Send us mail to the following mailing address:
TalkToMeMen.com Cancel
TL Holdings LLC
Suite 144
1409 Marlton Pike
Cherry Hill, NJ 08034
3.10. We may from time to time run promotions in which we ask Users or visitors for demographic information (like their Zip Code, State/Province or age). We may also run contests on TalkToMeMen.com in which we ask Users or visitors for demographic information. We use this data to tailor your experience, showing content that we think you might be interested in and displaying the content according to your preferences. We also use demographic information to determine eligibility for certain promotions and contests.
3.11. From time to time TalkToMeMen.com may ask Users to participate in surveys. Such surveys may ask Users for contact information (like their email address). We may use contact information from our surveys to send you information about our company.
3.12. TalkToMeMen.com may contain links to other sites. TalkToMeMen.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to review the policies of these sites.
3.13. TalkToMeMen.com also facilitates communication among Users through our on-site Mail system. Messages sent via Mail are identified only by your User name.
3.14. TalkToMeMen.com may use certain information collected from our Users in aggregate form to tailor our Users’ experience at the Site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying the content according to your preferences. TalkToMeMen.com may also supplement the information you provide by purchasing information relating to you from third-party data providers. TalkToMeMen.com uses this information to improve its marketing and promotional efforts.
3.15. TalkToMeMen.com uses cookies. Cookies are small amounts of data sent to a user’s browser from the TalkToMeMen.com Web servers and stored on a user’s computer’s hard drive. TalkToMeMen.com uses cookies to track the pages on the Site that our users visit. This allows us to collect aggregate information about usage on the Site. TalkToMeMen.com may also use cookies to deliver content specific to Users’ interests, and to keep track of Users’ User names and passwords so that Users do not have to re-enter them during a session. If you choose not to accept cookies, you will be unable to use the Site.
3.15.a. Google Analytics. When someone visits TalkToMeMen.com, we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior.
We do this to find out things such as a number of visitors to the various parts of the site.
This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone.
We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.
3.15.b. We use services provided by a third-party organization, iovation Inc., for the purposes of fraud prevention and account authentication purposes. iovation are based in the US. Their third-party services help us decide whether to accept transactions from electronic devices by analyzing device attributes and checking whether they have been associated with fraudulent or abusive transactions in the past. The service also helps verify your identity by registering and remembering devices associated with your account. We also report to iovation if we conclude that a device has been used in connection with a fraudulent or abusive transaction with us. iovation may track your activity over a network of different sites that subscribe to their services. Please see www.iovation.com and their privacy policy for more information about this service
3.16. TalkToMeMen.com uses your IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Generally, IP addresses tell us the location from which a person is connecting to us, what service provider the person is using and which parts of the Site the Site user is visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that your session will be tracked, but you will remain anonymous. We reserve the right to track IP addresses for the purposes of fraud prevention, and we reserve the right to release IP addresses to legal authorities.
3.17. If you send TalkToMeMen.com email correspondence, or if other Users or other third parties send us email or other correspondence regarding a particular User’s activities or postings on the Site, TalkToMeMen.com may collect such information.
3.18. TalkToMeMen.com strictly enforces and requires that all Users comply with its Anti-Spam Policy.
Our Disclosure of Your Information.
4.1. Except as explicitly stated herein, we do not sell, rent, or trade any personally identifiable information to third parties. In addition to the other circumstances of disclosure described in this Privacy Policy, TalkToMeMen.com may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties if you opt-in to having your personally identifiable information disclosed to such parties. When you consent to disclosure to such third parties, such third parties may use your information in accordance with their privacy policies, which may be less restrictive than this Privacy Policy. TalkToMeMen.com may also disclose your personal information to appropriate authorities and to banks associated with your User account in order to prevent or report suspected fraud and illegal activities, in order to prevent harm to any persons or if TalkToMeMen.com believes in good faith that the law requires it. In some cases, the government can compel the disclosure of information about you, and TalkToMeMen.com will comply, in which case you authorize it to do so. You also consent to TalkToMeMen.com disclosing information about you in connection with disputes involving other Users, and to actual or potential parties to a lawsuit or action that TalkToMeMen.com is or may become involved in, (a) if TalkToMeMen.com is required to do so, (b) if TalkToMeMen.com reasonably believes that such disclosures will potentially mitigate its liability, or (c) for TalkToMeMen.com to enforce its rights. TalkToMeMen.com may disclose some personally identifiable information to vendors and third-party service providers in connection with communications and payments to Users and other aspects of operating and promoting TalkToMeMen.com’s Site and Advisory Services. For example, TalkToMeMen.com uses other companies to deliver TalkToMeMen.com promotions, newsletter, and transaction emails, and we share your email address with this company unless you opt-out of receiving TalkToMeMen.com’s promotions by unchecking the box on the My Preferences page which asks if you wish to receive such mailings.
We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our newsletter and mailing campaigns.
For more information, please see these other company privacy notices.
Dyn's Privacy Policy, Active Campaign Privacy Policy, and Campaigner Policy Statement.
4.2. TalkToMeMen.com may also exchange personally identifiable information among TalkToMeMen.com Entities worldwide. If you are registering on any sites controlled by TalkToMeMen.com Entities located in the European Union, your personally identifiable information must be disclosed to TalkToMeMen.com affiliates outside of the European Union in order to allow Users worldwide to contact and be contacted by you. Therefore, as a condition of your Usership you hereby agree and consent to the sharing of your personally identifiable information with TalkToMeMen.com and TalkToMeMen.com Entities worldwide.
User Account Cancellation Procedures.
If you decide you would like to cancel your User account on TalkToMeMen.com, you will need to do one of the following:
Send us an email
including your User name and email address
by filling out a Customer Support Form asking us to cancel.
or
Send us mail to the following mailing address:
TalkToMeMen.com Cancel
TL Holdings LLC
Suite 144
1409 Marlton Pike
Cherry Hill, NJ 08034
Notification of Changes.
6.1. From time to time, We may revise this Agreement. We reserve the right to do so, and You specifically agree that We have this unilateral right. You agree that all modifications or changes to this Agreement are in force immediately upon posting. The updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting, and the prior version is of no continuing legal effect unless the revised version specifically refers to the prior version and keeps the prior version or portions thereof in effect. To the extent any amendment of this Agreement is deemed ineffective or invalid by any court, the parties intend that the prior, effective version of this Agreement be considered valid and enforceable to the fullest extent.
6.2. If We change anything in this Agreement, We will change the “Last Modified Date” at the top of this Agreement. The Agreement is located at (https://www.talktomemen.com/privacy_policy/).
You agree to periodically re-visit this web page, and to use the “Refresh” button on Your browser when doing so. Upon each visit, You agree to note the date of the last revision to this Agreement. If the “Last Modified Date” remains unchanged from the last time You reviewed this Agreement, then You may presume that nothing in the Agreement has been changed since the last time You read it. If the “Last Modified Date” has changed, then You can be certain that something in the Agreement has been changed, and You agree that You will again review the Agreement in its entirety and that You will agree to its terms or immediately cease use of the Website. Your continued Use of the Website, after any such revision, shall be deemed to be Your acceptance of all revisions.
6.3. Waiver. If You fail to re-review this Agreement as required to determine if any of the terms have changed, You assume all responsibility for such omissions and You agree that such failure amounts to Your affirmative waiver of Your right to review the amended Agreement. We are not responsible for Your neglect of Your legal rights.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with TalkToMeMen.com, please contact us.
Email: support@talktome.com
Mailing Address:
TL Holdings LLC
Suite 144
1409 Marlton Pike
Cherry Hill, NJ 08034
Copyright © 2010-2020 TL Holdings
TalkToMeMen.com is for entertainment purposes only.
Enable Nightmode
Find TalkersWomenShemalesRegister as a Talker
BlogsTalkToMeMen.com NewsBlogsFeatured Talkers InterviewsSextingPhone Sex News
Customer ServiceContact UsHelp
NewsTestimonialsAffiliate Program
PoliciesTerms and ConditionsUser AgreementPrivacy Policy2257 Statement
×Call TalkToMeMen.com's live TalkLine:Call
Inside the USA? Call:
1-800-MEN-1111
Outside the USA? Call:
+1-214-828-CHAT
Your account and pin numbers will be right here after you login.
Enter at least 3 characters.
No results found for your search.
Searching ...
×
×
×
Please use the controls below to play this greeting.
Why am I seeing this?Your web browser denied our attempt to auto play this greeting for you.
LoginCalled BeforeRegister NowDIPDIPPDIADIR
×
Member's Login Now:
Don't have an account? Create Account
Username or Email
Forgot?
Password
Login Now
×
Activate your Account:
Have you used our talk-chat lines?If so you have an account!
Claim My Account
×
Activate your Account:
Enter your Phone number below and we'll provide you with a PIN number that you'll use to verify your account when we call.
×
Activate your Account:
We're calling you now, please standby to pick up the phone and enter the PIN below when prompted. After verifying, a new dialog will display to register your account.
...
Please wait...
Go Back
×
Activate your Account:
Enter your Account and PIN numbers below and we'll to verify your account.
Continue
Go Back
×
Activate your Account:
Please fill out the following information to register your account.
Join our mailing list.
By checking this, I agree to the user agreement.
Register
Go Back
×
New here? Get $10 free:
Create an Account
Don't want an account?
Call: 1-800-MEN-1111
Pay directly over the phone.
Outside the USA? Call:+1-214-828-CHAT
If you do not set up an account you cannot Sext, Email, or Voicemail our Talkers.
×
Password Recovery:
If you forgot your password we will send you a link to reset it.
Username or Email:
Reset My Password
×
Your first $20 is free, join now:
Pick a Username
Email Address
Password
Confirm Password
Orientation: Please select an option.StraightGayBisexualWomanShemale
My Birthdate:
How did you find us? Please select an option.
Back PageBillboardBingFree 10.00 CardFriendGoogleHotMovies.comLink from a websiteMagazineMajor NewspaperNY PostRadioSexChat.comTelevisionTrade ShowWeekly City PaperWord Of MouthYahooOther
Join our mailing list.
By checking this, I agree to the user agreement.
Enter the code exactly as it appears on the advertisement. If you are redeeming a Talk Card scratch off to reveal the code on the back of your card.
You need to be logged in to use this.
Continue
You're almost there!
Continue
Enter the amount of credit below that you want to offer
to use to call you. This credit will expire in
days. You will not receive earnings for the credit used by the Caller.
Amount To Credit:
( - )
